Tanjiro! Long time no see!
Welcome to my mansion!
It's been a while!
Glad to see you looking well!
You too, Tanjiro.
I'll brew some black tea at 3:00!
I'll make pancakes too!
And smear a lot of butter!
Buttah? Pankehki?
And I barely know black tea.
Sweets! Bread! Pancakes!
Here you go!
Enjoy, Tanjiro.
Is there any right way to eat it?
Like this…
Tanjiro, say "ahh."
Okay.
How is it, Tanjiro?
It's so delicious,
my cheeks are going to fall off.
It's super-duper tasty, right?
Yes, totally!
Tanjiro, after you eat,
could you change into this?
To you who is ignorant of
What eternity means
It's time to show you the answer
Beyond the endless spiral
DEMON SLAYER: KIMETSU NO YAIBA:
HASHIRA TRAINING ARC
The reason why it sounded like an excuse
A weakness that draws in a fleeting future
You mistake it for strength
So detestable, so detestable
So disgraceful, so disgraceful
The heart that is so bleak
So dark, so dark
That it almost hides the moon
If only you weren't here
It sways and sways
Carrying on its intentions
Just like a flower
Taking it all away, taking it all away
It tears the heart just like a storm would
To you who is ignorant of
What eternity means
It's time to show you the answer
Beyond the endless spiral
Who awaits there
Ossu!
All right, everyone, move in sync!
Stretch out your hands!
Jump high!
Now, do a quick spin!
To enhance the sharpness
of your technique,
flexibility training is very important.
Let's stretch, stretch
and stretch some more!
No, no, not like that!
Could you step aside? I'll show you.
Ready?
ARRRRRRGGGH
Keep it up!
It's more brute-force training
than stretching.
-Come here!
-Huh?
Tanjiro, you do it as well.
What?
Are you ready?
Let's start!
Flexibility training…
is hell!
Tanjiro Kamado, I've been waiting for you.
EPISODE 5:
I EVEN ATE A DEMON
-I'm looking forward--
-Shut up or I'll kill you.
Huh?
Kanroji told me about you.
It seems you had quite a fun time
training with her.
Huh?
Enjoyable training, indeed.
You got a letter from Lady Kanroji.
How are you, Iguro?
Today, I had tea with Tanjiro
after training.
Tanjiro's cheeks almost fall off
when he eats or drinks something sweet.
He's so cute.
Kamado!
I won't go easy on you like Kanroji did.
I've just arrived and he totally hates me.
I've prepared your training.
You have to swing your sword
while avoiding these obstacles.
It's to improve your swordsmanship.
I see, and this place…
Is this an execution chamber?
Did these people who are tied up
commit any crimes?
Well, yeah.
The crime of being weak.
The crime of not learning.
The crime of wasting my time.
The crime of irritating me.
They committed those crimes.
Oh, dear, this is gonna be bad.
You'll use this.
I'll show you how to do it once.
That's all.
He can swing his sword accurately
between the members at that speed.
Your turn.
Don't hit me.
-Don't hit me.
Please don't hit us!
Do it quickly!
Okay!
Ridiculous.
How can you call that training?
I'll spar with you.
Attack me.
Attack…
Got it!
Don't hit me!
You're hesitating.
This won't accomplish anything.
Here I go.
Even in tight spaces,
I have to strike precisely.
Slow.
This is not good.
When dealing with Iguro, I must not
be concerned about the Corps members.
Get up. Let's start over.
A dreadful training begins.
Even though I'm using a wooden sword,
getting hit will still cause injury.
Iguro's attacks come between
these poor Corps members.
This is really bad!
Because his swordsmanship
bends in unusual ways!
Slow.
He's using the same wooden sword,
so why is it able to bend?
His attacks slither through narrow gaps.
Just like a snake.
Furthermore,
I can hear their inner voices
when I aim at the gaps between them.
Please! Please! Please!
Please don't hit me!
They're pleading with me not to hit them.
This is truly mentally taxing to hear.
Don't hesitate, you piece of trash.
My hands are trembling with tension
I've never felt before.
If I can't swing my sword precisely,
it'll be a disaster.
Oh, no! Sorry!
Kamado, how can you still go on
after all that training with the Hashira?
I don't want to cause trouble
for everyone.
I guess we have to do it as well.
You're right.
I bet this is going to sting the wounds.
It's definitely gonna hurt.
Ready, guys?
Okay, let's soak in.
Yeah.
All together.
One, two, and…
It stings!
DAY TWO
Slow.
There's no point in training
if you're that slow.
Understood!
Why would you slow down your stride?
It stings!
DAY THREE
Slow.
Slow!
Too slow!
Damn it. It stings.
DAY FOUR
What's the matter?
Are you just running, slowpoke?
I have to focus
only on sparring with Iguro.
In real combat,
if your sword gets caught in
a tree or a rock, it could be fatal.
It's the same as swinging the sword
while avoiding obstacles.
Now my I'm able to strike
more precisely than ever before.
Dodge Iguro's attacks…
so I can attack him back!
My attack hit him.
When my attack cut
the hem of Iguro's haori,
he said my training was over.
Thank you very much!
Get the hell out of here.
Just die already, you piece of trash.
Stop being too friendly with Kanroji.
It's sad to be hated until the end.
But why?
Was Shinazugawa's dojo this way?
You're wrong!
Turn right at that corner, you bird-brain!
I see. Turn right there.
Zenitsu?
He… Help me escape, Tanjiro!
Tanjiro, I beg you!
Escape from what?
I can't stand on my feet anymore!
It's impossible!
I've finally managed to escape this far!
I crawled over the walls
and disappeared like a gecko!
My life is in danger!
I'm gonna get killed!
Choose one.
Back to training or get killed by me.
No! Have mercy!
Calm down.
Nah! No! No!
Shut up!
KILL
Carry him
Oh, okay.
Sorry, Zenitsu.
Let's do our best together.
Long time no see.
I'll join your training today.
I'm looking forward to it!
Don't get carried away.
Listen, I don't acknowledge you.
That's totally fine.
I don't acknowledge you either.
You stabbed Nezuko, after all.
He's got nerve.
Shinazugawa's training was so harsh
that I understand why Zenitsu
became like that.
It was a simple striking training
where we could attack Shinazugawa.
We vomited…
and passed out.
It continued without rest, to boot.
Even Iguro gave us breaks.
When Zenitsu woke up, he blamed me
as if I had killed his parents.
You dumbo!
Ouch. Sorry.
Shinazugawa was especially hard on me.
If I let my guard down for even a second,
I'll get seriously injured
and end up back in recovery.
This is too much for the first day.
I'm a mess and covered in vomit.
I'm about to lose confidence.
Wait, big bro!
Genya's voice?
I want to speak with you.
Quit bothering me.
I don't have a brother.
If you don't knock it off, I'll kill you.
It's so different
from the sibling quarrels in my family.
Wanna give up?
Please don't, big bro!
Don't try to be friendly with me!
From what I've seen, you have no talent.
Just quit the Demon Slayer Corps.
Someone who can't use breathing techniques
shouldn't call himself a swordsman.
But I…
Wait, big bro!
I've always wanted to apologize to you.
Do your best, Genya. You can do it.
I don't care, seriously. Get lost.
But I…
I even ate a demon…
to fight until this point.
What?
What did you say?
You said, you ate…
a demon?
-He disappea--
-Genya!
How many more days is this gonna continue?
He's back! He's back!
That heartless man is back!
Get down! Pretend to be passed out!
Huh? Tanjiro?
Huh? He's gonna kill you, Tanjiro!
Why did you destroy the building?
Please stop!
What is this twisted and ominous sound?
That dude is on a rampage, right?
Are we gonna get beaten
outside of training?
What are you doing?
Do you want to kill Genya?
Of course not.
Killing him would be easy,
but it's against the Corps' rules.
I'll make him unable to recover.
However, I'll forgive him
if he quits the Corps right now.
You must be joking!
You don't have the right to do that!
You can't force him to quit!
Didn't you say earlier
that you don't have a brother?
Then don't interfere
with whatever Genya chooses!
Whether he has talent or not,
he decided to risk his life
to fight demons!
If you say you're not his older brother,
I won't let you interfere with Genya!
Without Genya, we wouldn't have defeated
the Upper Ranks Demons!
I won't let you hurt him beyond recovery!
You done?
Then I'll make you beyond recovery first!
Okay, here he comes.
Tanjiro!
This brat…
stopped my punch.
He kicked him!
Zenitsu! Please get Genya out of here!
Hey! You stupid!
Moron! Don't say my name! You fool!
Give a better signal!
Tanjiro!
His kick cut my ear
even though he just grazed it.
You've got some nerve!
Since you want to die,
I'll kill you like you want!
Wait, big bro!
Tanjiro has nothing to do with this!
Let's escape!
Who are you? Let go of me!
It's best to separate people
who are arguing!
Get some distance!
That guy's your older brother?
He's a total freak! I pity you.
Don't insult my brother!
I'm on your side!
Die, brat!
After that, the situation
just became a big mess.
The brawl continued until nearly evening.
Fool! Moron!
I received an official scolding
from the top brass.
My training with the Wind Hashira
was suspended…
NO!!
…and I've been ordered to refrain
from approaching him.
At the end of the day,
I was unable to reconcile
the Shinazugawa brothers.
I didn't mean for this to happen.
The mark isn't clear.
The training isn't bearing fruit.
Actually, it is.
You even went toe-to-toe
with that Wind Dude.
You're amazing.
Is that so?
Why's the Stone Hashira's house
so deep in the mountains?
This is just so stupid!
I think we're almost there.
What's wrong, Zenitsu?
I can hear something.
This way.
This place…
A waterfall!
Someone's there.
Nyo-Ze-Ga-Mon Ichi-Ji-Butsu-Zai
Sha-Ei-Koku Gi-Ju-Gi…
If you clear your heart and mind,
even fire feels cool.
Welcome to my training ground.
The flame that burns heaven
Truer than the truth
The voice of prayers and
The sounds of shouting
Are fleeting like winged insects
Why do those who devour lives
Beg mercy as if not knowing impurity
Those souls that win through
The darkness can only reach
Obtain that eternity
There's a feeling here
That doesn't know demise
Speak your dream, you strong one
A resound congratulating tune of eternity
Into the light that governs the sky
In the corner of the world that is messy
A blade of a sword
That still wriggles and resists
Grovels and struggles miserably
DEMON SLAYER: KIMETSU NO YAIBA:
HASHIRA TRAINING ARC NO. 5
This time I'll tell you about Iguro.
You're still here?
Don't tell me you're here
to bother Kanroji again.
No, that's not it!
It's the Taisho period secret.
Just get on with it.
Here we go, the Taisho period secret.
The name of the snake Iguro carries
is Kaburamaru.
Apparently, his eyes
have different colors from birth.
Finished? Then get lost.
Don't get too close to Kanroji.
Well, but…
Planning to get close to her?
Next up on Episode 6:
"The Strongest in the Demon Slayer Corps"
TO BE CONTINUED